<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-1.9.xsd">
    <changeSet author="laxika" id="20160622-1">
        <insert tableName="news">
            <column name="title" value="More improvements"/>
            <column name="release_date" value="2016-06-22 00:00:00"/>
            <column name="icon" value="update"/>
            <column name="message">
                <![CDATA[
Welcome Adventurers!

More small but useful improvements and bugfixes come with this patch. I know some of you really waited for these changes so here they are!

Improvements:
- The hammer was added as a requirement for all of the smithing recipes. You need to have one in your inventory otherwise you are not going to be able to create items via smithing. This was intended from the release of the skill but we missed to add it as a requirement before the skill went live.
- Added a new recipe named 'Recipe: Leather strap' and the item named 'Leather strap'. This item is added to some smithing recipes as a requirement. The recipes that require 'Leather strap' as an ingredient from now are: 'Recipe: Bronze gauntlet', 'Recipe: Bronze boots', 'Recipe: Bronze round shield', 'Recipe: Bronze kite shield'. Both the recipe and the new item are added as drops for monsters on the Farmfields.
- Replaced the old buttons that sat on the header at the Journal, Inn and Shop pages with new icons that similar to the ones used on the skill pages.
- Replaced the icons used on the Smithing skill's page with new ones. Hopefully, they will fit better for Smithing.

Bugfixes:
- Fixed that wearing shields in combat not gave Shield Defense experience.
- Fixed that ladder had more pages than users in the game so the last pages were empty. Now the count of the ladder pages are correctly generated.
- Fixed a bug on the Inn's chat page that enabled the players to type in more than the allowed count of characters into the chat's input field. When such a long message was sent, then the server denied it and it was not added to the chat's message wall. Now this rule is enforced on the chat and you can't type in longer messages than 254 characters.

Thanks, The Daggers & Sorcery Team
                ]]>
            </column>
        </insert>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>