<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-1.9.xsd">
    <changeSet author="laxika" id="20160620-1">
        <insert tableName="news">
            <column name="title" value="Smithing, a new tradeskill is released!"/>
            <column name="release_date" value="2016-06-20 00:00:00"/>
            <column name="icon" value="update"/>
            <column name="message">
                <![CDATA[
Welcome Adventurers,

We are happy to announce that a new skill, Smithing is arrived to the game. This skill will let you create various metal armors and weapons and also some supply equipment.

We also lowered the drop chances and prices of some items to make smithing more significant.

Improvements:
- Smithing as a new tradeskill is added to the game.
- Added 11 new recipes and 17 new items to the game. The recipes added are all for the new smithing skill and some of them have very low (less than 1%) drop rate. New item and armor types are also released in this batch of items like shield, dagger etc.
- Daggers are added to the game. They are balanced to have high damage and low attack to be a good fit for races with high Dexterity (eg Dark elf, Lizardmen).
- Shields are added to the game. We released two shields, a small one for rogue classes and a heavy duty kite shield for more tanky ones.
- Lowered the drop chances of 'Recipe: Leather gloves' and 'Recipe: Leather boots' by 0.5% from 1.5% to 1%.
- Lowered the drop chances of 'Bronze pickaxe' and 'Bronze axe' from 3% to 1% because we added a recipe for them to the Smithing skill.
- Lowered the drop chance of 'Frying pan' from 2% to 0.5% on all monsters because we added a recipe for it to the Smithing skill.
- Lowered the price of 'Tin ore' and 'Copper ore' from 5 to 3.
- Lowered the price of the 'Bronze bar' from 10 to 7.
- Increased the 'Salt' required for curing 'Deer skin' from 1 to 2.

Bugfixes:
- Fixed a bug that prevented the curing of Deer skin.
- Fixed that cooking the Apple pie recipe resulted in a 'Recipe: Apple pie' item instead of an 'Apple pie'.

Thanks, The Daggers & Sorcery Team
                ]]>
            </column>
        </insert>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>