<databaseChangeLog
        xmlns="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9"
        xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
        xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/1.9
                      http://www.liquibase.org/xml/ns/dbchangelog/dbchangelog-1.9.xsd">
    <changeSet author="laxika" id="20170717-1">
        <insert tableName="news">
            <column name="title" value="Improving the scrolling issues and fixing bugs"/>
            <column name="release_date" value="2017-07-25 00:00:00"/>
            <column name="icon" value="update"/>
            <column name="message">
                <![CDATA[
Welcome Adventurers!

As always, this week will start with a bunch of small but handy updates and bugfixes.

Improvements:
- The health of the user is shown on the combat screen. Later we plan on showing the monster's health too but we plan to do it in a form of a new skill that will help you analyze monsters for their health/mana points and weak points in combat.
- We split the character screen into five different panels to lessen the scrolling required to reach some of its parts.
- Renamed the 'Inn' to 'Tavern' to present a more welcoming look so hopefully more and more new people will find their way to the chat.
- The 'Banish undead' spell got a little buffing. Now it scales with the user's intelligence attribute.
- Added a new category called 'Guides' to the forum.

Bugfixes:
- 'Lesser healing potion' required 'Grimmy king's blood' instead of the cleaned one. This has been fixed.
- The cleaning page under the Herblore skill was unreachable. This has been fixed.
- 'Troll's vitality' spell not consumed mana nor gave XP. This has been fixed. Now it gives 20 XP and requires 10 mana to cast.
- Fixed the coin icons on the market screens.
- Fixed that the race bonuses were not given to the characters.

This is all for today. We are working on the vampirism curing quest with all of our available resources. If everything goes right it will arrive either today or tomorrow.

Sincerely, Daggers & Sorcery Team
                ]]>
            </column>
        </insert>
    </changeSet>
</databaseChangeLog>